Guide to the Weaver Social History Collection, 1913-1970 AIS.1964.19
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Assorted Publications and Materials, 1930-1970; VIII.
  - Pittsburgh Consumer's Cooperative. Statement of Purposes and Bulletin, July- August 1934 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Norman Thomas for President, Pittsburgh Committee, 1932 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - "A Survey of the Parties- 1932," by Devere Allen (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Communist Organizations in Southern California, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Progressive Citizens of America. Assorted Materials, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - "Fellowship of Faith," Movement, 1930s (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - "A Social Manifesto", undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - National Consumers League. Assorted Materials, undated (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - White Collar and Professional Organizations, 1943-1944 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - American Committee for Non-Participation in Japanese Aggression. Assorted Statements, undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Committee for A Boycott Against Japanese Aggression, 1938-1939 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Assorted Materials relating to Japan and China, undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - "12,854 Clergymen on War and Peace", 1935 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - American Committee for Chinese Industrial Cooperatives, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - American Boycott Against Aggressor Nations, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Western Pennsylvania Committee for Concerted Peace Efforts, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - American Committee for Struggle against War, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Congress Against War, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - National Council for Prevention of War, Assorted Materials, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - The Fellowship of Reconciliation, 1931-1933 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - New America Organization. Peace Proposals, 1939 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Pittsburgh Anti-War Committee, 1933 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Emergency Peace Campaign. Assorted Materials, 1930s (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Pennsylvania Committee for Total Disarmament, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - America First Committee. Correspondence, 1940 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - America First Committee. Aims and Purposes, undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - America League Against War and Fascism. Assorted Materials, 1930s (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - America First Committee. Pittsburgh Chapter, undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - America First Committee. Assorted Newspaper Clippings, undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - America First Committee. Correspondence, 1941 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Anti-Fascist groups. Assorted Materials, 1930s (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Neutrality. Assorted Statements, undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - American First Committee. Assorted Publications, undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Newspaper clippings on Neutrality, 1930s (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Friends of the Soviet Union. Assorted Materials, undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Pittsburgh Council of American-Soviet Friendship. Council views, February 1944 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Pittsburgh Council of American-Soviet Friendship. Assorted Material, undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Minutes of the campaign committee to send Mr. Hill as an observer to the Soviet Union, March- June 1936 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Russia. Assorted Newspaper clippings and Statements, 1930s (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - World Tomorrow Organization. Tabulation of the results of a questionnaire distributed at a peace meeting in Pittsburgh, October 1931 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Wartime relief for Europe. Assorted Appeals, Proposals, and Statements, 1940s (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Wartime relief for Europe. Newspaper clippings, 1940s (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - India Famine Emergency Committee, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - India League of America. Assorted Materials, undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - India League of America. India Today, 1940 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - India League of America. India Today, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - India League of America. India Today, 1942 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - India League of America. India Today, 1943 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - India League of America. India Today, 1944 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - India League of America. India Today, 1945 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - National Committee for India's Freedom. Voice of India, September, November, December 1944 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America. "Information Service", 1935 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Federal Council of Churches of Christ in America. "Information Service", 1936 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Policy Association. Purposes and Programs, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Policy Association. Correspondence, July- September 1933 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Foreign Policy Association. Correspondence, April- November 1934 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Foreign Policy Association. Correspondence, August- October 1935 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Foreign Policy Association. Correspondence, February- July 1936 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Foreign Policy Association. Correspondence, September- December 1936 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Foreign Policy Association. Correspondence, 1937 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Foreign Policy Association. Correspondence, January 1938 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Foreign Policy Association. Correspondence, September- November 1939 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Foreign Policy Association. Members, undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Foreign Policy Association. Attendance at meetings, 1933-1937 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Foreign Policy Association. Bulletins, March- April 1936 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Foreign Policy Association. Assorted Materials, undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Kingsley Association. Assorted Correspondence, 1918-1945 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Kingsley Association. Assorted Materials, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Kingsley Association. Workers and Volunteers, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Kingsley Association. "The Kingsley Record", September 1935 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Kingsley Association. Contributions from Hungry Club Members, 1917-1930 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Turner dismissal, University of Pittsburgh. Newspaper clippings, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Turner dismissal, University of Pittsburgh. Correspondence and Statements, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Brief history of the Irene Kaufmann Settlement, Pittsburgh, 1895-1936 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Crime and correction in Pittsburgh. Newspaper clippings, 1936-1942 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Crime and correction in Pittsburgh. Assorted Materials, 1936-1942 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Adult Education Program in Pittsburgh. Assorted Correspondence, 1937 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Adult Education Program in Pittsburgh. Assorted Materials, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Public Housing. Assorted Materials, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Public Housing. Newspaper clippings, 1930s (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Public Utilities. Assorted booklets and statements, 1930s (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Public Utilities. Newspaper clippings, 1930s (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Public Health Committee, Pittsburgh Chamber of Commerce. Assorted Correspondence, 1931-1933 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Inter-Chamber Health Conservation Contest. Pittsburgh's ranking, 1930 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Report on the Carbon Monoxide Survey Committee, 1932 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - William Penn Hotel Strike, 1934 (Box 18, Folder 21-22)
  - Irene Kaufmann Settlement. Board members, undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Religion and Labor Foundation. Assorted Materials, 1944 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - American Statistical Association, Pittsburgh branch. Members, ca.1934 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Community Executives' Roundtable. Members, undated (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Assorted lists of names, undated (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Aims and purposes, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Correspondence, 1934-1941 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Correspondence, January 1942 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Correspondence, February 1942 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Correspondence, March 1942 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Officers and Executive Committee, 1941 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Report of the Annual Meeting, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Financial Statements, 1935-1939 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Season Program Announcements, 1934-1941 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Announcements of individual meetings, 1935-1940 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Assorted illustrated program announcements, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Assorted materials pertaining to speakers and meetings, undated (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Summer reading suggestions, 1935-1937 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Questionnaires, undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. "News", 1936-1937 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Forum roundtable aims and purposes, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Forum roundtable program schedule, 1942 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Forum roundtable outlines of discussions, January-May 1942 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Community Forum of Pittsburgh. Assorted Materials, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Civic Center Forum. Correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Civic Center Forum. Committee members, undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Civic Center Forum. Assorted materials, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - "Listeners' Forecast", March 1939 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - "Listeners' Forecast", April 1939 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - "Listeners' Forecast", May 1939 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - "Listeners' Forecast." Notes, 1939-1940 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Speakers Service. Aims and purposes, undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, July- August 1938 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, September-October 1938 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, November-December 1938 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, January 1939 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, February 1939 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, March 1939 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, April 1939 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, May-August 1939 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, September-October 1939 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, November-December 1939 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, January 1940 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, February 1940 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, March 1940 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, April 1940 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, May 1940 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, June-August 1940 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, October-December 1940 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, January- March 1941 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, June- August 1941 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, September- December 1941 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, March- May 1942 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, 1943 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, 1944 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Speakers Service. Correspondence, 1945-1947 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Speakers Service. Financial Statement, 1939 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Speakers Service. Material concerning Francis S. Onderdonk, undated (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Speakers Service. Assorted Materials concerning Howard P. Davis, undated (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Speakers Service. Assorted Materials concerning Paul Harris, Jr., undated (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Speakers Service. Assorted Materials concerning Hedley Hepworth, undated (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Speakers Service. Assorted Materials concerning speakers, undated (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Speakers Service. "Report on Address," Francis S. Onderdonk, undated (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Speakers Service. "Report on Address," Howard P. Davis, undated (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Speakers Service. "Report on Address," Hedley Hepworth, undated (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Speakers Service. Materials from the Lecture League, undated (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Speakers Service. Materials from the "Open Forum Speakers Bureau", undated (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Speakers Service. Assorted Materials, undated (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - "The Truth About Public Relief," by the Association of Directors of the Poor and Charities and Corrections of the State of Pennsylvania, 1930s (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - "The Story of the Emergency Work Bureau, New York City", October 1930- August 1933 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Human Values published by the Community Fund of Pittsburgh and Allegheny County, March 1934, August 1936 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - "Questions and Answers relating to a Modern Plan for Public Assistance in Pennsylvania." Written by the Pennsylvania Committee on Public Assistance and Relief, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - "The Welfarian," published by the Welfare Fund of Pittsburgh and Allegheny County, January 1936 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - The Social Research Bulleting published by the Federation of Social Agencies of Pittsburgh and Allegheny County, June 1933 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Occupational Changes and Relief Activities in Allegheny County, March 1934 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Labor and Industry: State of Pennsylvania Monthly Bulletin, 1932-1934 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Monthly Bulletin: Pennsylvania Department of Welfare, April 1934 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Pittsburgh's Health: Published by the Department of Public Health, June, December 1933 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - "A Declaration of Principles Recommended to the Republican Party of Allegheny County", 1936 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Co-Op Bulletin of the Western Pennsylvania Council of Consumer Cooperatives, June-July 1937 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - "Political Decency Versus Party Regularity," by Edward O. Tabor, 1934 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - The Braddock Steelworker: An Income and Expenditure Study for January 1945 of Steelworkers in Braddock, Rankin, and North Braddock, Pa. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Woman's Club of Clairton, Pa., Yearbook, 1947 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - American Association of University Women, Pittsburgh Branch. Yearbook, 1939-1940 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Directory of the First Baptist Church, Pittsburgh, Pa., 1937 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - University of Pittsburgh Campus Index. Comments on faculty, causes, and organizations, undated (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - "Report on the Commission on Christian Social Action," Northern Baptist Convention, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Scottsboro United Front Defense Committee meeting minutes, December 3, 1934 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - "Money-Interest," by William Brown, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Treason in Congress: The Record of the Un-American Activities Committee, published by the Progressive Citizens of America, 1948 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - "Lawful Money Lectures." Published by the Sound Money Press, Inc., 1939 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - "Our American Dreyfus Case: A Challenge to California Justice," by Lilliam Symes, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - "The Future of Sea Power in the Pacific," by Walter Millis, 1935 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - "Capitalism and its Rivals," by Kirby Page, undated (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - "We Militarize," by Osward Garrison Villard, 1936 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - "Cooperation or Chaos," by Charles Douglas Booter, undated (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - "What Shall We Do About War," by Sherwood Eddy and Kirby Page, undated (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - "The Object, Methods and Achievements of the International Reform Federation, 1925 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - "The Design and Integration of Mutual Enterprises", undated (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Pamphlets and speeches by Chauncey E. Brockway, undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - "A New Standard of Ethics based on Universal Law," by Charles J. Simon, 1933 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - "Wltanschauung: A New Creed based on Universal Law," by Charles J. Simon, 1933 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - "A Message to the World based on the Universal Law," by Charles J. Simon, 1933 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Toward an American Revolutionary Labor Movement: Statement of Programmatic Orientation by the American Workers Party, 1934 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Toward an American Revolutionary Labor Movement: Draft Programs of the American Workers Party, 1934 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - "Pittsburgh's Pneumonia Problem," by C.J. Vaux, undated (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Masses, April 9, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - World Federation- Now: Organ of the Campaign for World Government, 1942-1944 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Illinois Women's Auxiliary of Progressive Miners of America. First Annual Report, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Social Work Publicity Council. News Bulletin, December 1935 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Labor Age, May 1932 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - The New International: A Monthly Organ of Revolutionary Marxism, December 1934 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Survey, April 1929 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - American Youth Congress News, August- September 1935 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - The New English Weekly: A Review of Public Affairs, Literature, and the Arts, May 1932 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Modern Monthly, July 1934 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Social Work Today, May- June 1934 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Survey Graphic, June 1934 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Survey, June 1, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Forum and Century, February 1932 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Survey: Journal of Social Work, February 1933 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - World Events: Published by the No Frontier News Service, March- April 1936 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - IPA News Bulletin: Published by the Inter-professional Association, October 1935, March- April 1936 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Social Security: Published by the American Association for Social Security, May 1934 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - I.R.A. Bulletin: Published by the International Relief Association, December 1935- January 1936 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Common Sense, July 1934 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Commonwealth College Fortnightly, 1932-1936 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Common Sense, July, August, September, November 1933 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Neighborhood: A Settlement Quarterly, June 1932 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Cooperation: Published by the Cooperative League of the United States, September 1934- January 1935 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Consumers Cooperation: Magazine of the Consumers Cooperative Purchasing Movement in the U.S., February, March, June 1935 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - National Wage Earner, November 1950 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Birth Control. Assorted Booklets and Statements, undated (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Birth Control. Assorted Correspondence, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Birth Control. Material pertaining to assorted organizations, undated (Box 23, Folder 3-5)
  - File of names (League of Social Justice ?), undated (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - The Genealogy of the Henry Family, 1919 (Box 23, Volume 1)
  - Works of F.J. Osterling (architect), 1904 (Box 23, Volume 2)
  - Mid-way Observers, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Mid-way Observers, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Henry, John M., undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - McNair, William N., undated (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Council For Peace And Social Action, undated (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Henry George Club, Pittsburgh, Pa., undated (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Henry George Fellowship, Pittsburgh, Pa., undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Henry George School of Social Sciences, undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Kingsley Association, undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - League for Social Justice, undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - National Economy League: Western Pennsylvania Branch, undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - United Christian Council for Democracy, Pittsburgh, Pa., undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Publications, undated (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Town Hall Crier, Pittsburgh, Pa., No. 1-4, 6-18, 2-23 February 12- October 1, 1936, undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - J.W. Correspondence, undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Weaver Notes, undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Borsodi, Ralph, undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - McNair, William N. Correspondence, undated (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - McNair, William N. Addresses, Speeches, undated (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - McNair, William N. Articles on William N. McNair, undated (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript (typed) of article on William N. McNair by John Weaver, undated (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - McNair, William N. Newspaper clippings, undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Bove, Mario L., undated (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Demmler, W.R., undated (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Allegheny Roundtable, undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - American Committee for Protection of Foreign Born, undated (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Americans for Constitutional Action, undated (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - ADA, undated (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Catholic Radical Alliance, undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Citizenship Clearing House for Western Pa., undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Civic Club of Allegheny County, undated (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Council Against Communist Aggression, undated (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Foreign Policy Association of Pittsburgh, undated (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Fraternal Order of Police: Fort Pitt Lodge #1, undated (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Greater Pittsburgh Council on Adult Education, undated (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Henry George School of Social Science, undated (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Hungry Club, undated (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - League for Social Justice, undated (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - League of Women Voters of Pittsburgh, undated (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Pittsburgh Real Estate Board, undated (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Pittsburgh Consumer's Cooperative, undated (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Public Affairs Forum Committee, undated (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - School of the Living, undated (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Squirrel Hill Merchants Council, undated (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Thrift Garden Committee of Allegheny County, undated (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - United Nations Association of Pittsburgh, undated (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - United World Federalists: Pittsburgh Area Council, undated (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Urban League of Pittsburgh, undated (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Yankee Freeman, undated (Box 26, Folder 35)
  - Biography (newspaper clippings), undated (Box 26, Folder 36)
  - Churches, undated (Box 26, Folder 37)
  - Education- Pittsburgh, undated (Box 26, Folder 38)
  - Land- Pittsburgh, 1935 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - Assorted Publications, undated (Box 27)
  - Assorted Publications, 1930-1950 (Box 28)
    The Center Information and Speakers' Bureau Bulletin; Speakers' Bureau Bulletins
  - Assorted Publications, 1930-1950 (Box 29)
    Numerous pamphlets on social issues; newspaper clippings
  - Assorted Publications, 1940-1950 (Box 30)
    Correspondence; newspaper clippings on WWII, Communism, Socialism, and Fascism
  - Assorted Publications, 1930-1950 (Box 31)
    Numerous pamphlets on social issues; newspaper clippings on FDR and politics
  - Assorted Publications, 1930-1940 (Box 32)
    The Militant; The Pittsburgh Record; numerous pamphlets; newspaper clippings
  - Assorted Publications, 1940-1960 (Box 33)
    Correspondence; Lecture topics; newspaper clippings
  - Assorted Publications, 1940-1960 (Box 34)
    The Freeman; newspaper clippings
  - Assorted Publications, 1930-1950 (Box 35)
    Numerous pamphlets on social issues, economics, politics, world events, philosophy
  - Assorted Publications, 1940-1960 (Box 36)